THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES
AI-GENERATED CONTENT
CASE 1:
THE SAINTS BASEBALL TEAM MURDER CASE
MURDER CLUB: LIAR'S TABLE
All right.
FIRST PLAYER ENTERS
This seems like a good spot.
Oh, boy.
CHOI YANGRAK
TV PERSONALITY
I guess I'm the first one here.
My goodness, what's all this?
GRAND VIBE
[Pani Bottle] Hello.
SECOND PLAYER ENTERS
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Pani Bottle.
Of course, I know who you are.
But I'll be playing someone else today.
PANI BOTTLE
YOUTUBER
I heard you have
three million subscribers.
Not quite.
It's a little over two million.
[Max Changmin] Hello.
- Hello, Yangrak.
- [Choi] Good to see you.
- [Max] It's nice to see you.
- Hi.
- [Max] Hello.
- Goodness.
- [Choi] You've gotten more handsome.
- [Max] Please.
[Pani] It's nice to meet you.
I'm a huge fan.
I'm not just saying that for the cameras.
MAX CHANGMIN
SINGER
- It's a nice table.
- [Choi] Right?
They put in a lot of effort.
It's new leather.
It's not an old table.
It's been newly upholstered.
It smells new.
You really think
they'd bring in an old one?
Hello.
- No way!
- Hello.
[Choi] Kim Hyunsoo.
- He's our MVP.
- Hello.
He's the Korean Series MVP.
[Choi] Congratulations.
- Oh, did his team win?
- Yeah.
He won with LG
and moved to KT this season.
I'm sure there was a good reason.
[Pani] Was it because
they recognized his talent?
Of course.
- I don't know baseball.
- He's Korea's best.
I'm a Hanwha Eagles fan
and hoped we'd win again at last,
but because of this guy,
our chances were ruined.
Anyway, thank you.
[Kim Seontae] Hello.
- [Pani] I see this guy all the time.
- [Choi] Gosh.
- Hello.
- This is…
- I saw him two weeks ago.
- Really?
- He's Chungju Man.
- Right.
Now the former Chungju Man.
KIM SEONTAE
FORMER PUBLIC OFFICIAL
LOOKS AROUND
What's with your outfit?
Are you wearing sweats?
- Well, the producers called me
- Yeah?
and told me to dress formally,
but I don't have a suit.
You'd think a public official
would own many suits.
- Yeah.
- We're quite close,
and since we first met
about two years ago,
he's always dressed the same.
So I once asked him
if he had any other clothes,
and he has many of the same type.
- Like a uniform?
- That's right.
Yes. I have a few.
Did you all get briefed on today's game?
I don't know the specifics.
I was just told it was a board game.
They didn't give me any other details.
You're very good at board games, right?
Board games are my hobby.
- Really?
- [Pani] But I'm not good at them.
Do you play board games, Yangrak?
I play games
like stone-flicking.
UNEXPECTED ANSWER
Oh, that's right.
- That's a classic.
- "Stone-flicking!"
- We both grew up watching that show.
- Yeah.
- [Max] It was a hit program.
- [Pani] It was.
[host]
Welcome to Murder Club: Liar's Table.
- Here we go.
- Looks like it's starting.
ROUND OF APPLAUSE
Today, you will be playing Murder Mystery,
a competitive deduction game
where your goal is to identify
the culprit hidden among you.
You will each be assigned a unique role
and play the game as that character.
There is only one culprit,
but every player has their own secret.
To win this game,
you are allowed to lie, conceal the truth,
and act deceptively.
The game consists of five rounds.
At the start of each round,
one clue will be revealed
to the entire group,
and all the players will pick out
one card clue and one object clue.
The card clues are confidential
and can only be shared
during private conversations.
The object clues
can be examined by all players.
After collecting the clues,
you will have a 15-minute discussion.
Starting Round 2, you will have time
for private conversations.
After the group discussion,
you will have five minutes
to talk secretly
in the private conversation zones.
In Round 5, the final round,
you will make your final vote.
After the final group discussion,
you will vote for the person
you suspect to be the culprit.
I'm not sure I really get it,
but all right.
LAUGHING
Can you handle this game?
- There are a lot of murder mystery games.
- Okay.
They're board games
where you each play a character
and try to find the culprit.
I've only played it once myself.
Was this your idea?
- No.
- [Choi] Did you choose this game?
No, I didn't know it'd be like this.
- He's insanely rich.
- [Pani] No, I'm not.
- So they spared no expenses.
- What?
How can you say that
in front of these people?
You're calling me rich
when I'm the poorest one here.
- He once showed his house on his channel,
- [Kim] What are you on about?
and it looked rather average,
but it was all a lie, right?
Yeah, there's a door at the very back
that leads to his real house.
- That's his real place.
- [Max] A mansion.
- Do you have a split personality?
- No, no.
Are you suspecting me already?
I think the person who'd be best
at pretending to be innocent
is Chungju Man.
- Me?
- [Pani] Yes. I know him well.
We did a survival show together,
and he's an expert at deceiving people.
Honestly, I didn't think
this production would be so big.
But with this kind of budget and cast,
why would they make me the culprit?
- That's a bit…
- That's true.
If I were a writer or producer,
I'd make one of you two the culprit.
But I don't have much TV experience,
and I'm new to this,
so wouldn't I be too obvious?
Then…
Honestly, if I might say so myself,
I'm known for being squeaky clean.
- You're lying already.
- [laughing] No, no.
I'm not.
- I think Pani Bottle is most likely.
- Yeah.
His glasses don't even have lenses.
- Yeah, they're just for show.
- See?
- It's a deceit.
But I'm a bad liar. I share everything.
I can't lie.
Yangrak, you tell fibs.
- I'm a joke-teller.
- He's a great liar.
That's different from lying.
You lied about being sober for a year.
You told your wife for a year
that you were a teetotaler.
Oh, it was a lie?
- How can you keep up an act like that?
- It was a long time ago.
I'm not a good liar.
[host]
Now, you will be assigned your roles.
Please choose one of the files
in front of you.
CHARACTER GUIDE:
PERSONALITIES, RELATIONSHIPS, ALIBIS
THE CULPRIT HAS BEEN CHOSEN
We're now playing these characters, right?
- I'm no longer Pani Bottle.
- Right.
- I'm…
- You're right.
I'm Yoon Minseok.
I'm a batting coach,
and I'm 49 years old.
A batting coach?
YOON MINSEOK
49, SAINTS TEAM BATTING COACH
- I'm with the Saints baseball team.
- Okay.
- I'm their manager.
- [all] Ah!
- You're the manager?
- Kang Dohyun, 55 years old.
The manager…
KANG DOHYUN
55, SAINTS TEAM MANAGER
I'm Jo Hajun.
- Jo Hajun.
- Yes, that's right.
The main sponsor of the Saints
is Geumseong Group.
- "Geumseong."
- And I'm their PR Strategy director.
JO HAJUN
30, GEUMSEONG GROUP PR STRATEGY DIRECTOR
I'm Lee Hyunsoo.
- Only your surname changed.
- That's right.
I'm Lee Hyunsoo.
I'm 26 years old,
and I was a rising star,
but another player surpassed me…
- [all laughing]
-…so now I'm just a reserve.
What's a reserve?
- It means a backup.
- He's not in the main lineup.
- I'm benched until someone gets injured.
- I see.
- Waiting for someone to get hurt.
- Yeah.
- It's the opposite of his reality.
- That's right.
I'm Kim Doyun,
and I manage a fan club.
I'm 34 years old,
and I'm a devoted fan
who collaborates with the team's sponsors.
KIM DOYUN
34, PRESIDENT OF SAINTS FAN CLUB
So you don't just manage the fan club,
but you also have business ties, right?
Yes, that's right.
I play a fairly big role.
Ooh.
You can tell he's done this before.
He's already asking sharp questions.
- [Hyunsoo chuckles]
- I've only played once.
END OF CHARACTER INTRODUCTIONS
- It makes all the difference.
- That's true.
SELECTED CHARACTER RESULTS
KIM DOYUN, KANG DOHYUN, YOON MINSEOK,
JO HAJUN, LEE HYUNSOO
[host] The murder took place
in the Saints' locker room.
The victim was Park Taeo,
the Saints' ace.
PARK TAEO
26, SAINTS' ACE BOUND FOR MAJOR LEAGUES
Right after winning the championship,
he planned to expose the team's corruption
before heading to the Major Leagues,
but he was discovered dead
at half past midnight that day.
Here is the first shared clue.
Please open the envelope in front of you.
1 SHARED CLUE IS REVEALED
AT THE START OF EACH ROUND
- Oh, gosh.
- Goodness.
OH, DEAR
ROUND 1 SHARED CLUE:
PHOTO OF THE CRIME SCENE
[Kang Dohyun] There's so much blood.
- How badly was he beaten?
- [Yoon Minseok] Is that cake?
- Cake?
- Cake and a ball.
It wasn't just any ordinary day.
- He just won.
- It's the day he won.
It happened right after.
- The ace was killed like this?
- How awful.
Round 1 will now begin.
First, pick out the card clues.
Every player
has a total of five card clues.
Each card contains a secret
that no other player knows.
In every round except for the fifth round,
the players can take one card
from the person they suspect.
Use the collected clues
to determine who the culprit is.
Do we pick our own cards
or someone else's?
Come on. Why would you pick your own?
Don't you know yourself?
Seeing how he just raised his voice?
- [Yoon Minseok] He seems agitated.
- I want to take one of his cards.
I guess the Saints associates
don't get along.
I'll take the fourth card.
I think you could be the culprit.
[chuckling] Jeez.
KANG DOHYUN TAKES KIM DOYUN'S CARD
They each took a card from each other.
PLAYERS CAN SHARE WHAT'S ON THEIR CARD
OLD ENVELOPE: DOHYUN
ARRANGING ILLEGAL SPORTS BETTING
LAPTOP: TAEO FANDOM ANALYSIS REPORT
WRITTEN BY DOYEON, SENT TO HAJU
I feel like
a feud between teammates
is the most likely scenario.
There's a baseball bat in the picture,
so I suspect the batting coach.
So I suspect the batting coach.
Then I'll go for…
Sponsors are usually the most suspicious.
THE CARD CLUES HAVE BEEN SELECTED
- Right, they're high-strung.
- [laughs] Yeah.
DOHYUN: MANAGER,
DOYUN: FAN CLUB PRESIDENT,
HYUNSOO: RIVAL, MINSEOK: BATTING COACH,
HAJUN: SPONSOR
Let's compare our timelines.
What were you doing and where were you
at the estimated time of the crime?
What's the time frame?
- Between 11 p.m. and 12 a.m.
- From 11 p.m. to 12 a.m.?
My team just won,
so I was doing press interviews
and appearing on the news.
Likewise, I was celebrating with the team,
moving around here and there.
At precisely 11:50 p.m., I just went home
since everyone was busy celebrating.
I was celebrating
with the fan club members,
shaking hands
and talking to the cheerleaders.
I couldn't play due to an injury,
so I got a checkup
from the team doctor at 11:40 p.m.,
and then slowly headed to the lockers.
[Yoon Minseok]
You didn't run into Park Taeo?
- No.
- [Yoon Minseok] Hmm.
Ooh.
[host] The evidence zone is open.
Please bring over one evidence each
and resume the group discussion.
[Yoon Minseok]
Oh, we bring them over ourselves.
EVIDENCE ZONE
- We popped the champagne.
- Yeah.
So people were drinking.
EACH PLAYER MAY COLLECT 1 OBJECT CLUE
PER ROUND FROM THE EVIDENCE ZONE
STARTLED
It's the bat.
There's a card under it.
AN OBJECT CLUE AND A MYSTERY CARD
I'll bring this over.
NOTICES SOMETHING
Wait.
- What?
- "Coach's bat."
ROUND 1 OBJECT CLUE:
BLOODY BASEBALL BAT
Why did they use my bat?
It's clearly a set-up.
I'm being framed.
They used my bat on purpose.
I'll go for locker number four.
The unlucky number.
There's blood on this ball.
Why would a ball be used in a murder?
- [gasps] Sneakers.
- [Yoon Minseok] They're bloodstained.
PROMOTION PROPOSAL
GEUMSEONG GROUP PR STRATEGY TEAM
Number two.
OBJECT FOUND
What's this?
It's very intriguing.
What is this?
WHAT'S THE FINAL CLUE?
[Jo Hajun] It seems very meaningful.
We're meant to share these, right?
We share all the object clues.
Keep your cards in your pockets.
CARD CLUES CAN'T BE SHOWN
DURING THE GROUP DISCUSSION
The first clue is already very telling.
I'll show you.
"I sometimes dream of a hurtling ball."
"Someone dies, but I survive."
"That's the punishment."
It shouldn't happen, but--
- It was written by Lee Hyunsoo.
- Yeah.
LEE HYUNSOO'S THERAPY NOTES
What did he mean by this?
"That's the punishment"?
Maybe it means he regrets it.
- He regrets his crime.
- Ah!
Seeing as these are therapy notes,
he must've been super stressed.
- For athletes, not being able to play…
- Right.
…is complete torture, right?
[Kim Doyun] That's right.
- There's also blood on this ball.
- [Jo Hajun] Yeah.
[Kim Doyun] Is it not related in some way?
- Look carefully at the ball.
- Yeah?
Only this part of the stitching is frayed.
Oh, you're right.
[Lee Hyunsoo]
For the seam to split like this…
It wouldn't split like this
from hitting someone.
[Kang Dohyun]
It had to be scraped across the ground.
Or maybe it was hit by another ball.
- That'd be hard to pull off.
- Way too hard.
- Toss batting.
- That's…
Maybe if you're a batting coach.
There's no way.
It's almost impossible.
- The bat is…
- It's labeled as "coach's bat."
- It's the batting coach's.
- It says it here.
- Let's say I'm the culprit.
- Okay.
What kind of idiot would use his own?
There are so many bats over there.
Look how many there are.
So why would I use my own to kill someone?
Every player has a bat
they naturally prefer.
- Isn't that right?
- That's right.
- They're all the same.
- Don't act naïve.
They're not all the same.
- Different weights.
- They don't weigh the same.
I thought the coach
was the most suspicious.
The victim had to be killed with a bat.
Accidents happen
when you're in close proximity.
And who was closest to the victim?
It was the coach.
The decisive clue was the coach's bat.
That's what convinced me.
They were probably close
until something made him snap,
which led to the accident.
I think he's the prime suspect.
Of course, we need to investigate
a bit more.
The bat looks clean, doesn't it?
- Coach's bats usually are.
- That's…
What this proves without a doubt
is that I'm not the culprit.
- That came out of nowhere. Why?
- They're trying to frame me
with a weapon they didn't actually use.
- That's your opinion.
- Right.
- But you're the prime suspect.
- [laughs] For now.
It's too obvious.
The game can't end this easily.
By the way, what's this?
That's a very big bloodstain.
Could he have banged
his head on the corner?
DID HE HIT THE BENCH CORNER?
The bat wasn't swung hard enough,
so he just fainted,
but his head hit the bench,
and that's how he could've died.
One swing of the bat
wasn't enough to kill him.
- It was a weak swing.
- He just fainted.
While falling over,
his head slammed into the bench.
[Lee Hyunsoo] Or maybe it was the ball.
WAS THE BALL THE REAL MURDER WEAPON?
But there's only one person here
who could throw a ball hard enough
to kill someone with it.
- Yeah, I agree.
- It had to be an athlete.
Are you a pitcher or a batter?
I'm an outfielder.
An outfielder?
If I had a stronger arm,
I wouldn't be a backup.
Oh, right.
You could be a one-tool player.
- All you've got is a strong arm.
- "One-tool."
There are players like that.
A one-tool player is unlikely
to be a backup.
You need at least two tools
The ball isn't clear evidence,
so I'm on the fence about Hyunsoo.
He doesn't have a clear motive.
He was jealous that Taeo was moving
to the Major Leagues,
so I don't think it was
reason enough to kill him.
In my opinion, he's the only person
who has a weak motive.
I took a card from Hyunsoo earlier.
- Lee Hyunsoo's.
- Yeah.
I took one of his cards.
If Taeo won the game
and moved to the Major Leagues,
Lee Hyunsoo would benefit from it
- since a spot would open.
- True.
- That means he can move up.
- Right.
If that's the case,
why would he need to kill Taeo?
- Right, a spot would open.
- Exactly.
- There's no need.
- Yeah, it would be a good chance for me.
It's a good opportunity.
The only motive would be
if you were on the list of corrupt people
he planned to expose.
But that's true for everyone,
including the director,
the coach, and the manager.
- The fan club manager might be exempt.
- Yeah, I have nothing to hide.
But the thing is…
One of the cards I picked
is about what Taeo was going to expose.
Whose card is it?
I took it from the director.
IT BELONGED TO DIRECTOR JO
He signed it himself,
and the sponsorship and PR costs
were substantial.
- The sponsorship and PR costs?
- Yeah.
Park Taeo's spending or his own?
It's an unofficial ledger.
-No one knows what it was spent on?
- No one knows.
A secret ledger for an entire team?
Is that possible?
It's not exactly a secret.
As you probably know better than anyone,
not everything the club decides
is openly disclosed,
especially in a role like mine.
I just did what the club told me to do.
I brought up the topic
to see how he reacted,
and it made me more suspicious.
The fact that he kept
that much money off the books
suggests he was up to something.
I also think he might've paid Hyunsoo
under the table.
- I took a card from the manager.
- Okay.
This makes things a bit tricky.
There's an old envelope.
It's an internal document
of the Busan District Prosecutors' Office.
Busan District Prosecutors' Office?
You once broke the law.
What are you talking about?
You arranged illegal sports bets
and got a suspended indictment.
No, I never did that.
- You arranged illegal sports bets?
- No, that wasn't even a thing back then.
What are you talking about?
The time's going by so fast.
- Yeah.
- Faster than I expected.
ROUND 1 CARD CLUES
OLD ENVELOPE, LAPTOP, NEWS ARTICLE,
STADIUM CLEANER'S MEMO, UNOFFICIAL LEDGER
[host] Before Round 2 begins,
- here is a new shared clue.
- [Yoon Minseok] I'll open it.
"October."
"D-2, D-1. It's nearly over."
- There's a tear.
- Something's been ripped out.
"My sorrow has made another person sad."
"It's a cycle of tragedy."
"I want it to end quickly."
There's nothing after that.
I think this is the last page.
- Does it belong to the culprit?
- I'm not sure what it is.
"I want it to end quickly"?
Oh.
It was mine.
I'm not the culprit,
but I have secrets
that no one can find out.
No one's focusing on that diary right now,
so that's great.
I think we'll just slide past it.
They'll forget all about it.
[host] Round 2 will now begin.
Please exchange your card clues.
The manager gets first pick.
- You keep taking mine.
- It's because you're next to me.
YOON MINSEOK TAKES JO HAJUN'S CARD
- I feel compelled to take yours, Director.
- Jeez.
I think the manager's a bit suspicious.
I think so too.
Why me?
Unbelievable.
- I also think it's you or the coach.
- We got a hard-earned victory.
What kind of dumb manager
would kill his championship hero?
But you lost him to the Major Leagues.
- And you have a crime record.
- Okay.
You shouldn't accuse innocent people.
Jeez.
Let's go.
Let's head to the Evidence Zone.
It's the locker room
security footage report.
There's no footage
between 11 p.m. and 12 a.m.
It's a voice recording of Park Taeo.
Let's listen to it together.
This bag is full of items.
What's this?
[Changmin inhales sharply]
A NOTE?
[Yoon Minseok] Hold up.
- This is a love letter.
- [Jo Hajun] Exactly.
Was it unrequited love?
We found a really unusual
piece of evidence.
Rather surprisingly,
there was a romance amid all this.
"Taeo, you've been pulling away."
"You didn't take my calls today,
and you say no one can find out."
It seems to be a secret relationship.
- Park Taeo didn't want it.
- Hmm.
I might be biased,
- but it looks like fan-letter stationery.
- Yeah.
It might be from a fan.
Yes, it could be from a fan.
- Right?
- So it might be nothing?
[Kim Doyun] Yeah, it might be from a fan.
It seemed like a fan letter to me.
When it comes to stars and their fans,
some fans can get a bit obsessed.
They express their love
in an unhealthy way.
Since it was written
on fan letter-type stationery,
I'm suddenly very suspicious
of Kim Doyun, the fan club president.
I think this is
a fan club merchandise bag.
- Fan club merch?
- Yes, it's filled with Saints merchandise.
A Saints key ring.
And most importantly,
there's an emergency medical kit.
It says, "Good luck, Park Taeo!"
That means he wasn't in good health.
It seems he had to take insulin shots.
- Insulin?
- Yeah, it's at the bottom.
Doesn't that mean he was diabetic?
It was well-known to his fans.
All his fans knew about it.
He had Type 1 diabetes,
but he worked hard
to manage his condition.
But could a fan get hold of this
on his behalf?
I'm not sure about that.
What would happen
if he didn't get his insulin shot?
- Would he die instantly?
- He wouldn't die,
but it'd affect his performance.
If he doesn't get his shots on time--
As the team manager,
I was aware of Taeo's condition.
- You knew about it?
- [Kang Dohyun] Of course, I did.
I'm his manager, after all.
So that means these items
most likely belonged to Park Taeo.
I thought it was a fan club bag at first,
but seeing how it contains insulin
and based on what we've discussed,
I think it was Taeo's bag.
- I also have--
- What's that?
- I have a recording device…
- Okay.
…with a record of Taeo's calls.
I'll press play.
Director Hajun.
I don't think I can take on
this promotion campaign.
Honestly, I plan to leave the team soon.
So, I don't think it'd be right for me
to keep promoting the Saints.
I'm going to notify the club.
I'm sorry.
END OF CALL
What's this about, Director?
- There was a conflict.
- You had a clash.
There were no hard feelings at all.
I worked with Park Taeo for a long time
on various promotional campaigns.
- I'm well aware of that.
- Right.
But this season,
there were some difficulties
due to scheduling conflicts.
I think he was referring
to a scheduling issue.
- I don't think that was it.
- Right?
Was there a demand
for a cut of the profit?
A kickback?
He and I didn't engage
in those kinds of financial dealings.
- I swear.
- I picked one of the director's cards.
He wrote an unsent text
begging him to do the campaign.
A CAMPAIGN THAT COULD
COST HIM HIS LIVELIHOOD?
It seemed like
he really wanted Taeo on board.
- He seemed desperate?
- Yes, he did.
- He needed it to happen, so--
- That goes against what you said, no?
Yeah, so what he just told us
doesn't quite align with the evidence.
- Right. You mean his statement?
- So, that's a bit… Yeah.
As I understand it, a baseball club,
its players, and middlemen like me
have multiple discussions
about whether or not
to move forward with a campaign.
The batting coach
seemed a bit suspicious of me,
but getting suspicious
over something like that
is pretty amateurish thinking.
If he was planning to move next season,
there was no reason not to do
the campaign this season.
- Right?
- I suspect something happened before that.
It was just an excuse.
Yeah, next season was just an excuse.
- It wasn't just about the campaign.
- [Lee Hyunsoo] I agree.
It wasn't just a campaign.
It's like you said earlier.
The campaign was just an excuse.
I'm guessing there was more to it.
In regard to that other thing,
I actually wanted to talk
about the card I picked.
- What is it?
- So the thing is,
the cards I picked
in this round and the last round
both point to the same person.
At Park Taeo's estimated time of death,
there was a witness statement
claiming that an elderly man
entered the locker room.
CLEANING STAFF
AN ELDERLY MAN WHO ENTERED
THE LOCKER ROOM AT AROUND MIDNIGHT?
- An elderly man?
- What are you talking about?
Elderly?
It says that there's no security footage
between 11 p.m. and 12 a.m.
-It's the only gap in the footage.
- Right.
- Among us--
- So who made that statement?
- Don't make things up.
- No, I'm not.
- Are you lying for entertainment?
- No, no.
[laughing]
Hear me out.
- I picked two cards, right?
- Right.
I can't go into the specifics,
but Park Taeo demanded answers
from the manager.
- Gosh.
- Do you remember what that was about?
No, not at all.
The card I picked
also points to the manager.
- It's about me and Park Taeo?
- Yes.
It's a note the manager wrote.
"I made that kid a champion."
[Kang Dohyun] Yeah, I trained him.
"But he's trying to kill me."
- That's what he wrote.
- Park Taeo?
It says, "He's trying to kill me."
That's just a common expression.
- Common?
- It's an everyday phrase.
He must've had a secret
that could be exposed.
- I have no secrets.
- Plus…
- We found out earlier--
- You had legal trouble.
Oh, please. That was ages ago.
- He has a criminal history.
- I don't.
Game-fixing!
IS KANG DOHYUN A CORRUPT MANAGER?
At that time…
What are we talking about right now?
Who am I answering to?
- What is it you want?
- Start from the beginning.
- Say your piece.
- Whatever that is.
- It's your last chance to defend yourself.
- When I was a teenager,
sports betting wasn't even a thing.
- And what else?
- Game-fixing.
Why would I do something like that?
"Crime of arranging illegal sports bets."
"Suspect, Kim Dohyun.
Suspended Indictment."
You definitely have a record.
A suspended indictment means
a crime was committed,
but I wasn't punished for it.
- That's right.
- He acknowledged it.
- He confirmed it.
- No.
And that's got nothing to do
with this murder case.
- He pressured Park Taeo to fix the game.
- Why does it matter?
And he thought Taeo
was going to expose him
before moving to the Major Leagues,
and that's why he…
- You're a backup on the same team.
- Right.
- Player Lee Hyunsoo.
- Yes?
Did I ever fix a game?
- A backup wouldn't matter.
- He couldn't help you.
It's not like I can play.
- No, I just mean…
- How can I fix a game?
There aren't that many players.
Game-fixing in this era?
What a load of bull.
Darn it.
This is just absurd.
Why are you attacking an innocent man?
You lot are scary.
There are too many red flags.
He's the most suspicious,
based on what I know so far.
When Park Taeo exposed the team,
the person with the most to lose
was the team manager.
There were a lot of clues,
and too many of them
pointed to the manager.
It turned out he was a criminal.
How can we play a game with a criminal?
I think they're all suspicious.
They're teaming up to get rid of me.
There must be an accomplice.
The culprit didn't act alone.
What kind of manager
kills his player with a bat?
It's an unthinkable crime.
ROUND 2 CARD CLUES: ACCIDENT REPORT,
TEXT MESSAGE, HANDWRITTEN NOTE
Starting Round 2,
the private conversation zones are open.
[host] Players can talk in private
for five minutes.
We can pick anyone, right?
I pick Pani.
PLAYERS CAN PICK SOMEONE
FOR A PRIVATE TALK
People are simple-minded.
- Come with me.
- Me? Okay.
I had some questions for the manager.
If you suspect me,
it means you're a simple-minded man.
But honestly, the bat is…
- Come on, that's way too obvious.
- That's true.
- But honestly,
- It's too easy.
- I called you over because you're second.
- Okay.
- I'm the second suspect?
- Yeah.
- You're second on my list.
- Okay.
My top suspect is the manager.
What do you think? Who's your top suspect?
- Is motive the right word?
- Yeah?
The key issue is that Park Taeo
- was going to blow the whistle.
- Yeah.
The people who had secrets
that could be exposed
are the manager and director,
based on what we know so far.
- That's right.
- That said, as for the director's motive,
a canceled campaign
isn't reason enough to kill someone.
There are two options.
That means he's not the culprit,
or there was more
to the promotional campaign.
As for the manager,
the most shameful thing
he could do in the sports industry
that had to be kept a secret
and could even harm the industry
is game-fixing.
- It would destroy his reputation.
- Exactly.
It could rock the entire sports industry.
That's how serious game-fixing is.
So, I suspect it's one of them.
Are you not the culprit? Be honest.
- There's no evidence.
- Is it really not you?
Well, there was the bat.
- You might've clashed with the players.
- Not at all.
- Positive?
- Yeah.
Then, I change my mind.
- You're not second. You're third.
- Okay.
The second suspect is the director.
But the first suspect
is definitely the manager.
There was something
I really wanted to ask you.
Who is Cheol Ongsik?
- Who?
- Cheol Ongsik.
I've never heard of them.
- Oh, come on.
- I mean it.
I didn't bring this up earlier
in front of the group,
but you sent money
to someone called Cheol Ongsik.
There's a record of the transaction.
I did no such thing.
I might've purchased
some supplies and materials.
Supplies and materials?
Yeah, it might be a bank transfer
for something I bought.
- But I have no idea who that is.
- All right.
You're making it out as if
I sent money to someone
for some corrupt reason.
Hear me out. That kind of transaction
shouldn't happen.
- Even I know that.
- Not in this day and age.
Right, not in these times.
But nowadays,
who wires a hundred million won?
I've never transferred
a hundred million won. [laughs]
- Dohyun.
- Listen.
I never did that.
JO HAJUN TOOK A CARD
FROM KANG DOHYUN IN ROUND 2
EMAIL: TRANSFER HISTORY
AMOUNT: 100,000,000 WON
- Dohyun.
- Yeah?
- You need to be honest.
- [laughs]
I've never been the kind of person
to twist the facts
just to fit the narrative.
All right, then.
Let's talk about the fan club.
Did you send that letter to Park Taeo?
- The fan club?
- Yeah.
- Fan letter?
- That letter we found
about how he was avoiding calls
and growing distant.
No, I like women.
- No, what I mean is--
- I don't like men.
- What was your name again? Doyun.
- Yeah.
- As Doyun.
- Not as Chungju Man.
- I'm speaking as Doyun.
Does Doyun like men?
I might like men in real life,
but Doyun doesn't.
- Oh, it's the other way around?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it might be
a different story in real life.
- Doyun's definitely into women?
- One hundred percent.
No doubt about it.
Well, maybe it's not a love letter.
It could just be genuine concern,
telling him to look after himself.
As the fan club president,
I really supported and admired him,
but interpreting it like that
is going a bit far.
- But didn't you write it?
- No, I didn't.
It wasn't me. Why would I?
So you didn't write it?
- I brought a card with me.
- Okay.
It actually concerns the manager.
- He's guilty of something else.
- Ah!
But I'm holding back
until I've had a few more discussions.
Ah.
But he is guilty of one more thing.
There's more corruption.
I can't go into the details,
but it's related.
- It's related to another third party.
- Mm-hmm.
There's a lot pointing
to the manager right now.
- I heard that he has
- Yeah?
- another guilty secret.
- Okay.
The fan club president told me.
- He's guilty of more corruption?
- Yeah.
This handwritten note.
HE'S TRYING TO KILL ME
I find it the most suspicious.
He wrote about an unbeatable champion.
Park Taeo's the only one
who fits the bill right now.
Then maybe it's this.
Park Taeo couldn't tolerate
such corruption,
so even if it cost him,
he felt he had to expose
the manager's misconduct.
Who do you think is the culprit?
[laughing] I think it could be you.
- You suspect me?
- Yeah.
Wait. Why do you think that?
Overly devoted fans
can turn into stalkers.
- You suspect me because I'm a fan.
- Yeah.
Park Taeo might've found you bothersome.
He had so many fans.
- [laughing] That's a bit…
- So if a fan is too persistent…
But the logic is a bit flawed.
I killed him because I'm such a big fan?
- What about the insulin?
- No, maybe you were too persistent,
constantly reaching out to him,
telling him what to do.
- Stalking?
- Yeah.
But that's--
And not to mention
giving him insulin
and supplying him with medication.
That's a doctor's job.
But it was sent by a fan, right?
That's merch for the fans,
but I didn't send them.
LAUGHING
Who else among us is a fan?
It's not like I sent it.
You're the fan club president.
- Yeah, I am.
- You're the most likely sender.
It's clearly from a fan.
- The fans…
- Yeah.
That's a bit of a stretch.
Then the bat and glove manufacturers
must be guilty too.
- Honestly, our coach
- Yeah?
- is also a bit suspicious.
- Right.
- So I--
- He's suspicious.
And the bat is the decisive evidence.
- You're right.
- Yeah, the bat.
You might wonder who could be that stupid,
but that might actually be
a genius strategy.
- To be honest--
- [host] Your time is up.
- Round 3 will now begin.
- Okay.
Oh, man.
I wanted to get to know the manager more.
I wanted to see
if he acted differently in private.
But nothing changed.
He just kept pushing his own point.
He suspected me, but his reasoning
was that I killed Park Taeo
because I loved him so much.
He said a fan's obsession
could lead to murder.
I just thought,
"Oh, he's talking nonsense."
I think the fan club president
is kind of twisted.
I can't read him
even when he's right next to me.
I can't figure out his sexuality,
and the fact that he made insulin…
Isn't that the job
of medical professionals?
I find that really suspicious.
As for the sponsor, Director Jo…
Is that his name?
He had some financial issues,
so I reckon he kept making
unreasonable demands.
This card shows the email record
of his transaction history.
It was deposited by Kang Dohyun,
the team manager.
He sent a hundred million won
to someone named Cheol Ongsik.
What kind of crazy person
sends that much money,
leaves a record of the transaction,
and then forgets about it?
He's the most suspicious so far.
[host]
Starting Round 3, the CCTV zone is open.
Use the password cards
to access the security footage.
- Password?
- What password?
- The alphabet cards we saw earlier.
- Is it this?
This was a password?
CCTV PASSWORD ON BONUS CARD
FOUND NEXT TO OBJECT CLUE
- [host] Here is the third shared clue.
- What's this? A cake?
ROUND 3 SHARED CLUE: VICTORY CAKE
AND BLOOD TEST RESULTS
Oh, the baseball bat
wasn't the murder weapon.
There was a cake.
Since he was diabetic,
wouldn't cake be bad for him?
WAS THE CAKE THE REAL WEAPON?
This photo's torn up.
Check this out.
- I think this will determine it.
- Round them all up.
- This photo…
- What is it?
- Well, that solves it.
It's over. This is the decisive evidence.
This is huge.
Oh, there are multiple CCTVs.
Let's see.
Isn't that the director?
[Kang Dohyun] That's him, right?
- Yeah, it is.
- It is.
Director Hajun.
What's going on here?
It looks like a family photo.
Oh, my, the director…
[Kim Doyun] The director is the culprit.
[theme song playing]
Translated by Hannah Og Nam